Are you sure you want to plead guilty?
I'm sure.
Give up your accomplices, and you could get a reduced sentence.
I acted alone.
Then sign here.
Dad took all the blame
and kept me completely out of it.
Everyone thinks
he was the one who kidnapped and killed the hostage.
But the truth is,
the truth is,
he wasn't the one who killed that little boy.
It was me.
It wasn't your fault that child died.
It was an accident, Ding Ning.
Your mom...
Does she know about this?
No one knows about it.
It's not that I haven't tried telling her,
but every time I worked up the courage
to bring it up to her,
she would instinctively resist it.
She probably just didn't want to recall
her relationship with my dad anymore.
Besides, she has a new life now.
Even if I told her, it wouldn't change anything.
It really wasn't your fault, Ding Ning.
Why did your father
have to bring a five or six-year-old child
to a kidnapping scene,
and make you take care of another child?
What do you think you could have done back then?
It's been twenty years.
Ever since that day,
I've been locked inside that closet.
Locked in there for twenty years.
I originally thought
that for the rest of my life,
I'd never dare to open that closet door again.
But then I met you.
Lao Yu,
you and Awu
are incredibly important to me.
When I'm with you two,
I truly feel happy and grounded.
It feels like everything I missed out on
has been made up for.
But now,
the reality before us
is something we have to face.
Listen to me,
I don't want to lose you guys,
but I also can't watch another child
be wrongly accused.
That child...
I have to save him.
To save that child,
there is only one way.
You need to cooperate with me,
and use Zhao Yijie to infiltrate Mr. Bi's inner circle.
No problem.
We'll do exactly as you say.
Thank you
for trusting me,
and for treating me
as your own family.
That brings me a lot of comfort.
Really.
Life really works in mysterious ways.
It brings you to despair,
then gives you a glimmer of hope.
Yang A'wu...
is your biological grandson, isn't he?
I've actually always wanted to confess this to you,
but I honestly didn't know
how to bring it up.
Well, now,
I can finally let this secret out.
Do you want to hear it?
It's just you today.
Yes.
I already know.
I can handle this.
You should tell the police the truth.
I said, I can handle this.
If they hadn't arranged for you to go there,
if they hadn't pushed you time and again,
you wouldn't have done it at all.
I know they even gave you
psychological training for interrogations.
It definitely included
when a lawyer advises you to tell the truth,
how you should resist.
But, Lu Zhiyong,
you're not out of options.
If you change your mind,
Fan Dong and I will do everything we can
to get your life back to normal.
What about the money?
You should only earn the kind of money
that lets you sleep at night.
I don't care if I can sleep at night.
I only care if my mom can.
Before,
my mom worked five jobs a month,
only slept three or four hours a day,
and made just three thousand yuan a month.
Now,
she makes thirty thousand a month.
Lu Zhiyong, you don't understand.
After I'm convicted,
they'll also let me
live in a big house like the ones my dad built.
His name is Fang Quan.
Quan as in spring water.
Twenty-six, unmarried.
He worked at a parts factory,
but he got out.
Before you guys stabbed him to death,
he had just bought a high-speed train ticket home,
planning to go back to Lingchuan County for the New Year.
Just like your mother,
he wanted to work hard and make money in this city.
I'm not listening!
No, you want to hear it.
In fact, you want to hear it the most.
You think about it day and night, you can't sleep.
It's all you think about.
He didn't die!
I didn't kill anyone!
You also want to know,
if you took every one of those stabs yourself,
what it would feel like.
You can't wait to be punished.
You are completely trapped in
the moment you killed him.
You can never...
Take me back!
I want to leave!
Take me away!
I'm not waiting for my mom anymore!
I want to go back!
Take me away!
You should only earn the kind
of money that lets you sleep at night.
After a few years in there,
you'll still be young when you get out.
When you get out,
you and your mom will be able to live
in a nice house like the ones your dad built.
You can even have a car.
And
you and your mom can get
a very well-paying job.
What do you say?
Have a seat.
Did you figure it out after our last chat?
I'll do as you say.
Okay.
But Ding Ning,
I'm not the only examiner this time.
What do you mean?
After finishing this case,
you can make me a law firm partner?
A law firm partner
is worthless in your eyes.
I know your ambition.
What I can tell you is,
the false litigation base was a mock exam.
Lu's case
is the real test.
Ding Ning.
Everything you want
to have
is just one step away.
So could you,
no matter how far your investigation has gone,
help that kid plead guilty as soon as possible?
Okay?
Lu's case has ruined too many people.
Fan Dong,
Lu Zhiyong himself, his mom,
and even...
even Yang A'wu.
I guarantee you,
Awu will absolutely not
get involved in this murder case.
But you've seen Lao Yu's usual worries.
If one day Lu loses his mind
and confesses to the burglary with Awu,
things will get much more complicated.
I know.
Good.
Then I'll go be a math teacher now.
Come on, math class.
No math. No class.
No class.
Okay.
Then let's just chat.
About what?
Let's talk about Sister Ding Ning, okay?
Do you like her?
I do.
What do you like about her?
She lets me have my way. She's so warm.
Compared to Grandpa, who do you like more?
I like both.
But I still want to take care of Grandpa more.
Good boy, you've grown up.
What do you think of Dad?
Dad?
Do you mean the dad who's locked up?
I mean me.
Right.
What do you think of Zhao Yijie?
Never mind.
Did he give you a hard time?
It was okay.
He just urged me
to hurry up and wrap up Lu Zhiyong's case.
Then what are you hesitating for?
I don't know.
Lao Yu,
I just feel something is wrong.
I know what you're thinking.
In your previous nursing home rape case,
Chang Yu also made you rush the process
and ignore the truth.
So this time you feel that
everything has gone back to square one.
But this time, you're not alone.
Compared to a year ago,
you're no longer fighting on your own.
He deliberately told me just now
that I'm not alone anymore.
It felt like there was a hidden meaning.
If I had more time,
I could play with you a little longer.
It's fine.
But this time is really different.
This matter
involves way too many people.
So, let's get through the process quickly.
I'll accompany you to the next stage.
He has already figured it out.
Anyway, his strategy has changed.
It seems he's getting serious.
Look,
with everything before,
the focus of his strategy was control.
But this time,
he seems to really be letting me do as I please.
So he clearly knows I'm investigating him,
and he knows you're looking into him, too.
It's not even hard to guess
that we've teamed up against him.
Yet he still lets us do whatever we want.
That's what's so strange.
I don't know what you think,
but I feel like
Zhao Yijie has truly changed.
That's impossible.
This guy,
he can't change his nature.
Trust me.
Anyway, no matter what,
right now,
the only thing we can be sure of is
that Lu Zhiyong's case
is a major concern for Zhao Yijie and his people.
And I think
used such extreme methods
to protect a kid...
Is that kid really that important?
What's your relationship with him?
Or is there some force behind him
making you do this?
I had no choice.
I believe
the true culprit's father is Mr. Bi himself.
Let's go over the situation.
Three days ago, Zhou Hao told me
that a colleague from the finance department
went and had a fight with Xu Ruqing.
"How do you expect me to record this?
If it can't be explained clearly,
I'll be the one held legally responsible!"
Director Xu, the case files.
They're on the desk. Take them yourself.
Zhou Hao took the chance to secretly photograph some documents.
He found that on New Year's Day,
which was after the murder
and before Lu turned himself in,
under the expenses of the charity foundation,
there were a few strangely large disbursements.
The payee was a company
that had never appeared before.
And the address of this company
belongs to a jewelry store.
Hello, sir.
How may I help you?
What's interesting is
that on the second day of the New Year, this jewelry store
hired a store supervisor.
So this is
what Lu meant when he mentioned
the source of his mother's 30,000-yuan monthly salary.
And even if someone investigated,
it'd be hard to find anything fishy about it.
The Rujie Charity Foundation
paid out such a large sum of money
because on the surface,
they were investing in this jewelry store.
Investing?
Which was then converted into his mother's salary.
It's a method that's hard to detect.
What about the house?
Didn't Zhao Yijie say
he would buy them a house?
Zhou Hao looked into that, too.
You wouldn't even believe
how quickly they managed
to come up with this solution.
Especially those
whom I had once forgotten,
who made significant contributions
to our group's development.
Please welcome them to the stage!
Today, I have decided
to give each of them a house.
The time Lu Zhiyong's parents received the gift
was exactly
three days after Lu Zhiyong turned himself in.
This is Zhao Yijie taking advantage of
Lu's father being injured, right?
Right.
The acquisition of the house
was framed as compensation for his father's paralysis,
a payment he was denied for years
by the real estate company.
And the official reason given
was that the real estate boss grew a conscience
and wanted to give back to his employees.
Isn't that complete fantasy?
But there's no need to be so discouraged.
If this case is really as you say,
something that happened over the New Year,
then there must be loopholes
that Zhao Yijie's people had to cover up.
There's one more person you need to watch out for.
Lao Kong.
Lao Kong?
Lao Kong is already very wary of you.
So as early as that day,
before you came clean to me on the bridge,
I had already arranged for a rookie
to keep an eye on Lao Kong.
Who?
It's not Navel Song, is it?
He's notorious.
Do you think that's credible?
Lao Kong.
Everyone knows him.
But this guy is not to be messed with.
Let's hear it.
See that?
Some lawyers,
just like you and Zhao Yijie,
look glamorous.
And some
are like Chang Yu, focusing on volume.
I'm like them, just hustling for scraps.
The bottom tier.
But the difference you can see
isn't the biggest difference.
What is the difference?
The biggest difference is
whether you have someone like Lao Kong.
What kind of man is Lao Kong?
Lao Kong does all the dirty work.
The people around him
are absolutely ruthless.
But if you try to buy Lao Kong off now,
at his current level,
he doesn't answer to anyone exclusively.
Didn't you say he works for Zhao Yijie?
Yeah.
That's because he chose to be Zhao Yijie's man.
Let's put it this way.
A lot of people owe him favors.
If you want to replace Zhao Yijie,
you really need someone like Lao Kong.
And the more, the better.
Compared to Lao Kong, what do you think
you're missing?
What am I missing?
What do I lack?
Well, here's the thing.
You see,
tailing Lao Kong
is no easy task.
It's much harder than tailing Yu Songfan.
And if he catches me,
I might even lose my life.
Name your price.
Well, this time,
I'm not asking for money.
I'm risking it all.
I want something bigger.
Even though I can never be
someone like Lao Kong,
you still have to
prove that you can replace Zhao Yijie.
So this time,
if I find something more valuable,
I want...
Everything you need is in here.
And what about what you need?
Are they all in there? In the private room?
But Yu Songfan...
knows all his colleagues' secrets,
yet never said a word.
He really is a gentleman.
For you to use these secrets
in such a short amount of time
to turn half the court's staff
into your friends...
You're quite the talent yourself.
For gear that can't go wrong, trust Navel Song.
Here's a little gift for you.
This here
is a long-range tracker and bug.
You won't find it on the market.
The signal won't drop even three meters underground.
It records even breathing sounds crystal clear.
Hope you can put it to good use.
Thanks.
Ding Ning
Navel Song, Yu Songfan...
coming straight to us would be more reliable.
We shouldn't meet in public so often.
You need to learn to ask for help,
instead of carrying everything yourself.
We have plenty of resources at our disposal.
I can help you investigate a lot of things.
I have my ways.
Please trust me.
I know how to deal with Zhao Yijie.
Of course I trust you.
But when you tell me nothing,
it puts me in a very passive position.
I can't even protect you.
At the very least, whatever you know,
I should know too.
No, you can't.
Zhao Yijie is too good at
mixing truth with lies.
He uses all sorts of smokescreens
to divert your attention.
And to put it bluntly,
you don't even know the rules of this game.
Then help me understand them.
Fine, I'll give you an example.
When you and Zhao Yijie vanished and reappeared back-to-back,
I even suspected for a moment that you were turned,
and that the car crash was just a ruse.
Let me give you another example.
If he found out I was your mole,
he absolutely wouldn't expose me.
Instead, he'd use it to his advantage.
How so?
He'd still take me to meet his gang,
except they'd all be scapegoats.
He'd put on a full show
to make me believe it's real.
But the real masterminds
would remain hidden in the dark.
He might have even guessed
that we'd be arguing like this today.
Guessed I wouldn't adapt well to working with you,
and that I'd feel untrusted.
And then make you completely lose faith in us,
and finally believe
that Zhao Yijie's gang is the best path for you.
Yes.
He wants to use you
to grind away my remaining faith,
and make me become just like him.
If you're really that worried,
you can use this to find me.
At the same time, the gravity of each atom
collapses toward the center,
delivering pressure and heat.
Since the sun's mass is so immense,
its gravity
can build up extremely high temperatures.
The higher the temperature,
the faster the atomic nuclei move.
When it reaches 10 million degrees,
the electromagnetic force of the nuclei
will be unable to stop
the collisions of the fast-moving nuclei.
And so,
the strong nuclear force instantly fuses them,
releasing an enormous amount of energy.
This is nuclear fusion.
It's the sun's...
Teacher, I need to use the restroom.
Go ahead.
That's everything.
Alright, let's go.
Awu!
Brother Kevin!
It's good that he moved away.
Now he won't have to worry
about those online crazies hurting his family.
I'll be leaving in a few days too.
Where to?
Back to the UK.
By the way.
Since you're here,
let's make another trip.
I wanted to copy Lu Zhiyong,
but you won't let me pick the lock.
So what are we going to do now?
It's... It's that old man.
Grandpa!
He's the old man you took to the police station,
right?
Grandpa, it's me.
Do you remember me?
Must be nice being Lu Zhiyong.
Navel Song provided a piece
of evidence that can completely
overturn Lu Zhiyong's murder case.
What evidence?
When Navel Song was tailing Lao Kong,
he found out that after the incident, Lao Kong
had been doing one thing.
That is, confirming that on New Year's Day,
there were no other surveillance videos
capturing Lu Zhiyong covering for the real killer.
Shouldn't Fan Dong's side
be doing the exact same thing?
Yeah.
But the problem is, they didn't get them.
Lao Kong and his guys already got two.
Bought with money.
There's only one left that slipped through.
Only their place has a security camera.
So how much cash do we have?
Why do you need cash?
To buy it, obviously.
What year is it?
Who uses cash anymore?
We can just transfer it.
Good point.
But we still need a reason.
They won't just sell it because you ask.
Wouldn't they find it weird?
Why don't we just tell him
our child went missing nearby,
so we need his security footage
to take home and look through.
We'll appeal to his emotions.
You'll be the mom,
and I'll be the grandpa.
Then we give him 10,000 yuan...
Ten thousand?
In case we can't move him,
10,000 yuan will definitely sway him.
Look at these small shops.
10,000 yuan is a month's income for him.
Right?
Alright.
Here, this is 50,000 yuan.
Hello.
Hold on, hold on.
If we can use this footage
to find my grandson,
you'd be our family's great benefactor.
As his grandpa,
along with his mother,
we will be grateful to you forever.
Don't mention it.
Here, this is the card.
Keep it safe.
I hope you find the child soon.
We'll get going then.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
What do you want to buy?
No, thanks.
This guy looks familiar.
He must be Lao Kong's man.
What do we do now?
Let's follow him for now.
Hold on a second.
I saw you sneaking around just now. What are you up to?
Hand it over.
ID card. ID card.
Yu Songfan.
What?
Lao Yu.
There's dashcam footage.
Yeah.
The dashcam.
Where is it?
Have you ever wondered
why good people have to go through eighty-one trials,
while bad people
only have to lay down their butcher's knife
to become a Buddha on the spot?
Before you try to brainwash me again,
I want to ask a question.
Making Lu the scapegoat,
does this also reflect your so-called...
ideology of protecting good deeds in your own way?
No.
But it can't be helped.
If the real culprit gets caught,
someone will be implicated.
It will affect all our future plans.
What plans?
Your escape plan?
You swore to me
that it was for some ideals and beliefs.
But in the end,
isn't it all just a facade
for your illegal activities?
Then why don't you look on the bright side?
Didn't Lu get a chance
to change his destiny against all odds?
If it weren't for this,
with his background,
how many years would he have to struggle
before he could afford a house and a car?
Before he could get a decent job?
Before he could cross class barriers
and live the life he's always wanted?
What right do you have
to manipulate someone else's life?
What gives you the right to choose for him?
I didn't.
This was exactly his own choice.
I told you,
I don't force anyone to make choices.
Don't be fooled by the fact that Lu is just a kid.
He knows he has to seize this opportunity.
Doing a few years in prison
means he'll be set for life when he gets out.
Tell me, if this kind of opportunity
were posted online,
wouldn't people fight tooth and nail for it?
Save that crap for someone else.
The real culprit's father is Mr. Bi, right?
Yes.
I want to see him.
Don't give me any more "today" or "tomorrow".
I want a specific date.
Next week.
I'll take you to see them next week.
However,
there are two conditions.
The first condition
is that I finish Lu Zhiyong's case, right?
And the second?
There's something that would make a great gift.
What?
Local News
Jiangliu Vice Mayor, Bi Wenhao,
visited Binjiang Subdistrict, Fulin District yesterday
to inspect the city's appearance and environment.
Bi Wenhao led officials from the Urban Management Bureau,
Housing Bureau, and Environmental Protection Bureau
on a site visit to the main and minor roads,
historical building clusters, and riverside landscape.
Afterward,
Bi Wenhao will visit the Fulin District Court in Jiangliu
for a symposium with Vice President Cai Dongchu
and Deputy Chief Judge Qiu Qiming of the Criminal Division,
to research criminal trial work.
Where is it?
Where?